export const Data = [
  {
    "question": "1) 12.5% of a solution having milk and water in the ratio 24 : 25 is removed and replaced with water. Find the ratio of milk and water in the solution if this operation is done a total of three times.",
    "options": ["21 : 64", "27 : 64", "8 : 27", "27 : 33", "21 : 43"],
    "correctOption": 4
  },
  {
    "question": `2) Rahul removes a fraction of undiluted spirit and replaces it with water to avoid detection. He
    does so on two continuous days. If spirit now accounts for only 64% of the solution, what
    fraction of solution did he remove daily?`,
    "options": ["1/3", "2/3", "1/4", "1/5", "1/6"],
    "correctOption": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "3) A cask is full of wine but it has a leak in the bottom. When one-fourth of the cask empties out because of the leak, the cask is replenished with water. Next when half of the cask has leaked out, it is again filled with water. Finally when three-fourths of the cask leaks out, it is again filled with water. What is the percentage of wine in the cask now?",
    "options": ["9.375%", "8.33%", "7.2%", "7.5%", "6.66%"],
    "correctOption": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "4) When 10% of a solution of milk and water is removed and replaced with water, the ratio of milk and water becomes 3 : 1. Find the ratio of milk and water before the water is added to the solution.",
    "options": ["2 : 1", "4 : 1", "5 : 1", "5 : 2", "4 : 3"],
    "correctOption": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "5) From a 100 litre container having milk and water in the ratio 8 : 7, 10 litres of solution is removed and replaced with 20 litres of milk. Again 20 litres of solution is removed and replaced with 30 litres of milk. Find the amount of milk in the solution now.",
    "options": ["112.5", "105.6", "93.7", "87.5", "85.6"],
    "correctOption": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "6) Water equal to 10% of a solution of milk and water is added to the solution. Now 10% of the solution is removed. If now the ratio of milk and water is 3 : 1, find the ratio of milk and water in the initial solution.",
    "options": ["27 : 40", "27 : 13", "33 : 7", "33 : 40", "27 : 33"],
    "correctOption": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "7) In a particular dilution technique, 10% of the solution is removed and replaced with the diluter. If we start with pure alcohol, minimum how many times would the operation need to be performed to bring the percentage of alcohol below 65%.",
    "options": ["3", "4", "5", "6", "7"],
    "correctOption": 2
  },


  {
    "question": "8) The average sales for the months January to March is 40, the average sales for the months March to June is 50 and the average of the months January to June is 45. Find the sales in the month of March.",
    "options": ["30", "40", "45", "50", "60"],
    "correctOption": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "9) The average of Sachin after 80 one day matches is 55. If Sachinâ€™s target is to increase his average to 57 after the next one day match, how much should Sachin score in the next one day match? (Average = total run / total number of innings)",
    "options": ["213", "214", "215", "216", "217"],
    "correctOption": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "10) When a student weighing 68 kgs joins a group of 8 students, the average of the group increases by 1.5 kgs. Find the average of the original group.",
    "options": ["53", "54.5", "56", "57.5", "None of these"],
    "correctOption": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "11) From a group of 12 students with average weight being 72.5 kgs, two students leave. Because the two leave, the average of the group falls to 71.25 kgs. Find the average weight of the two students who leave the group.",
    "options": ["78.5", "78.75", "79.25", "157", "157.5"],
    "correctOption": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "12) If a student weighing 70 kgs joins a group of n students, the average of the group increases by 1 kg. If the new student weighed 55 kgs, the average of the group would have declined by 2 kgs. Find n.",
    "options": ["3", "4", "5", "6", "7"],
    "correctOption": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "13) Ten years ago, the average age of a couple was 27 years old. Today also the average age of the couple and their baby is 27 years old. Find the present age of the baby.",
    "options": ["3", "4", "5", "6", "7"],
    "correctOption": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "14) By what does the average of all odd numbers between 50 and 130 differ from the average of all multiples of 3 between 20 and 160.",
    "options": ["0", "1", "2", "3", "4"],
    "correctOption": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "15) The average of n consecutive natural numbers is 17.5. What is the largest value that n can assume?",
    "options": ["Infinite", "34", "35", "36", "18"],
    "correctOption": 1
  }
]
